modenus.com 2018-10-04

# Privacy Policy - Modenus

Thank you for your interest in using the collection of online resources located on the website modenus.com (the “Site”). Your privacy is important to us and we have prepared this Privacy Policy to explain to you how we collect, use, and share information we obtain through your use of the Site. This Privacy Policy does not govern our use of any information you provide to us when you call us, write to us, or communicate with us in any manner other than through the Site. Because the Internet is global, information about you that we collect or that you submit may be transferred to, processed in, and held in countries (including the United States) other than the one in which you reside. **By using the Site, you explicitly consent to such use of your information and agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy is effective as of August 1, 2010.**

#### 1\. Information We Automatically Collect.

We automatically collect certain information to help us understand how you use the Site (which we will refer to in this Privacy Policy collectively as “Usage Data”). For example, each time you visit the Site we may automatically collect your IP address, browser and computer type, access time, the Web page from which you came, and the Web page(s) that you access during your visit. We also use cookies (which are small amounts of data sent from a web server to your browser that are stored on your computer’s hard drive) to keep track of your use of the Site, to validate your identity, to remember your password and preferences, to tailor the Site to meet your personal interests, and to improve the quality of the Site. In addition, third parties who place advertisements on the Site may also collect information through cookies to ensure that their advertising systems and technologies work properly and to allow them to track responses to their advertisements. Cookies set by these third parties are governed by the privacy policies of those third parties. Generally, you can set your browser not to accept cookies or to notify you if you are sent a cookie, giving you the opportunity to choose whether or not to accept the cookie. Please note that if you do set your browser not to accept cookies, certain areas of our Site may not function properly.

#### 2\. Information You Choose To Submit.

You can visit the Site without telling us who you are or revealing any information by which someone could personally identify you (which we will refer to in this Privacy Policy collectively as “ **Personal Information** ”). If, however, you wish to register to become a member of the Site, you are required to provide certain Personal Information (e.g., your first and last name and e-mail address), and we ask that you also provide a user name and password. We use your Personal Information to fulfill your requests for products and services, to improve our services, and to contact you from time to time about us, our Site, and our products and services.

#### 3\. Our Information Sharing Practices.

(a) **Generally.** Except as otherwise described in this section of our Privacy Policy, we will never share your Usage Data or Personal Information (which we will refer to in this Privacy Policy collectively as “User Information”) with any third party without your permission.

(b) **Advertisers.** From time to time, we may share your User Information to enable third parties who serve advertisements on the Site to deliver advertisements that will be relevant to you. We will not share any such information, however, in a manner that would enable the advertiser to personally identify you.

(c) **Aggregated Data.** From time to time, we may share aggregated User Information with third parties. We will not share any aggregated data, however, in manner that would enable the recipient to personally identify you.

(d) **Third-Party Marketers.** If (at the time you register to become a member of the Site or thereafter) you affirmatively authorize us to do so, from time to time we may share your Personal Information with third parties so they may contact you regarding goods or services in which you may be interested. If you have authorized us to do, and later decide that you would no longer like us to disclose your personal information to third parties for the third parties’ direct marketing purposes, please contact us as noted below in “Choice/Opt-Out.”

(e) **Service Providers.** From time to time, we may enter into relationships with third parties who provide services to us (e.g., data management and storage services or credit card processing services). In those circumstances, we disclose User Information that is necessary for such service providers to perform those services and require that they maintain the confidentiality of such User Information.

(f) **Public**. The Site enables you to create and edit a profile containing your photograph and information about you. The photograph and information you include in your profile will be available to other users of the Site.

(g) **Other Disclosure Scenarios.** Notwithstanding anything in this Privacy Policy to the contrary, we reserve the right, and you hereby expressly authorize us, to share any User Information: (1) in response to subpoenas, court orders, or legal process, or to establish, protect, or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims; (2) if we believe it is necessary in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, fraud, or situations involving potential threats to the safety of any person or property; (3) if we believe it is necessary to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding significant abuse of the Site’s infrastructure or the Internet in general (such as voluminous spamming, denial of service attacks, or attempts to compromise the security of information); (4) to our parent company, subsidiaries, joint ventures, or other companies under common control with us (in which case we will require such entities to honor this Privacy Policy); and (5) if we are acquired by or merged with another entity.

#### 4\. Public Information.

Your profile is public, and by adding any photographs or information to your profile, you are authorizing us to share such photographs and information publicly. Also, there may be areas of the Site (e.g., the in-stock section, message boards, discussion rooms, and other online forums) in which you are able to post information that will be available to all other users of the Site. By choosing to use these areas, you understand and agree that anyone may access, use, and disclose any information that you post to those areas.

#### 5\. Choice/Opt-Out.

We offer you the opportunity to control whether we share your Personal Information with third parties for their direct marketing purposes. You may request that we do so at the time you register to become a member of the Site or at any time thereafter by accessing and updating your privacy settings through your “My Account” page. In addition, if you have previously authorized us to do, you may request that we no longer share your Personal Information with third parties for their direct marketing purposes by accessing and updating your privacy settings through your “My Account” page. Please note that sometimes these requests may take up to ten business days to process and that we are not responsible for removing information about you from the database of any third party to whom we were authorized to disclose your Personal Information prior to processing your request. Even if you do take advantage of these opportunities, we reserve the right to send you messages relating to the Site (e.g., about changes to this Privacy Policy or our Terms of Service) and to contact you regarding any goods or services you have ordered or goods or services that may have been ordered from you.

#### 6\. Modifying and Deleting Your Personal Information.

If you would like to modify or delete from our database any User Information you previously submitted to us, please let us know by accessing and updating your profile. Please note that any User Information that we have copied may remain in back-up storage for some period of time after your request, and that if you delete certain information you may not be able to order services in the future without re-submitting such information. Also, please note that we will maintain User Information in our database whenever we are required to do so by law.

#### 7\. Security.

We have implemented reasonable measures to help protect your User Information from loss, misuse, or unauthorized access or disclosure. Unfortunately, however, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, while we strive to protect your User Information, we cannot guarantee its security.

#### 8\. Links.

The Site may contain links to other websites. We are not responsible for the privacy practices of any such other website and urge you to review such practices prior to submitting any information to such websites.

#### 9\. Children’s Privacy.

We are committed to protecting the privacy needs of children and we encourage parents and guardians to take an active role in their children’s online activities and interests. The Site is not intended for and may not be used by children under the age of 14. We do not knowingly collect information from children under the age of 14 and we do not target the Site to children under the age of 14.

#### 10\. Changes.

We may update this Privacy Policy from time to time. If under any such update we make any material change to the way in which we treat your User Information, we will inform you of such change via e mail or by posting a notice on relevant areas of the Site. Any updated version of this Privacy Policy will be effective as of the date set forth therein.

#### Questions.

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please feel free to contact us by e mail at [talktous@modenus.com](mailto:talktous@modenus.com)
